The screen went dark and there you were
화면이 꺼지고 네가 나타났지
A stranger staring back at her
낯선 이가 그녀를 다시 노려보고 있었지
No filter left to hide behind
더 이상 숨을 필터는 없었지
Just hollow eyes and tangled mind
그저 텅 빈 눈과 엉킨 마음뿐
Black mirror black mirror on the wall
검은 거울아 검은 거울아 벽에 걸린
Which version of me answers when you call
네가 부르면 어떤 내가 대답할까
The glass is cold the light is gone
유리는 차갑고 빛은 사라졌네
But something keeps reflecting on
하지만 무언가 계속 비치네
She scrolled through lives that were not hers
그녀는 자기 것이 아닌 삶들을 스크롤했지
Collected likes like souvenirs
좋아요를 기념품처럼 모았지
The battery died the room went still
배터리는 방전되고 방은 고요해졌지
And silence was the bitter pill
그리고 침묵은 쓰디쓴 약이었지
Black mirror black mirror on the wall
검은 거울아 검은 거울아 벽에 걸린
Which version of me answers when you call
네가 부르면 어떤 내가 대답할까
The glass is cold the light is gone
유리는 차갑고 빛은 사라졌네
But something keeps reflecting on
하지만 무언가 계속 비치네
Black mirror black mirror on the wall
검은 거울아 검은 거울아 벽에 걸린
Which version of me answers when you call
네가 부르면 어떤 내가 대답할까
The glass is cold the light is gone
유리는 차갑고 빛은 사라졌네
But something keeps reflecting on
하지만 무언가 계속 비치네
The glass is cold the light is gone
유리는 차갑고 빛은 사라졌네